Guide to the photograph album Royal Air Force in Iraq and Sharjah during WWII - Volume II AD.MC.013.v2
Akkasah: Center for Photography (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Blank page., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk07_z02; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
- An excerpt from "The Listener" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., 18 May 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk08_z01; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Printed Materials; English Writing; Iraq; Masirah Island, Oman; Arabian/Persian Gulf; Sharjah, United Arab Emirates; Musicians
- Blank page., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk08_z02; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
- A diagram of a bomb distributor., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z01; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
- Blank page., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z02; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
- An article entitled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z03; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Printed Materials; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Airplanes; Transportation; English Writing; Al-Fallujah, Iraq; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z04; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Airplanes; Transportation; Printed Materials; English Writing; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Al-Fallujah, Iraq; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z05; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Men; Individual Portraits; Airplanes; Transportation; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Printed Materials; English Writing; Uniforms; Royal Air Force; Military/Soldiers; Medals/Insignia
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z06; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Printed Materials; English Writing; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Airplanes; Transportation; Men; Individual Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z07; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  English Writing; Printed Materials; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Buildings; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z08; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Skeletons; English Writing; Printed Materials; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z09; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Airplanes; Transportation; Printed Materials; English Writing; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Royal Air Force; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z10; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  English Writing; Printed Materials; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Al-Fallujah, Iraq; Bridges; Men; Group Portraits; Royal Air Force; Military/Soldiers
- An article titled "Assyrian Levies - The Battle for Habbaniya 1941" (Please note: This material has been digitized in its entirety and contains racist and culturally insensitive remarks)., Circa 1943 - 1944; nyuad_pa000002_zbk09_z11; Sainty, C. J., Active circa 1941-1943; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD-MC-013_v.2)
  Men; Military/Soldiers; Royal Air Force; English Writing; Printed Materials; Al Habbaniyah (Habbaniya), Al-Anbar Province, Iraq; Uniforms; Group Portraits; Musical Instruments